Hi Gas welcome back to my channel, actually this is the
video that I had posted a
few days ago, I had a
small accident one day, I mean
I am giving a small review of that, you can see,
whatever had happened, so on
18th I had a small accident, the
track had hit me from behind, the front was
also touched a
little and there is more damage in the rear
and the dryer bumper at the back was also damaged,
you can see the video of that, so this is the video, I
mean what is the process, I had got this
thing done in TCP Motors,
I had digital insurance, it was zero de
fast party,
so the thing is that almost my ID
value is also fine, so first
of all, if God forbid, if anything like this happens to you, then
first of all, if I had
online insurance, if
you have online insurance, then you will have to
register the claim online, if yes, you
mean, if you are
giving the car to the service center, then if they will do it there, then it is
okay, so first of all  You have to register the claim online,
after that they will contact
you and look at the vehicle and one
thing when I had registered the online claim on Delete, the
customer
executive had said that I am giving you a link,
give the photo of the damaged vehicle there, that is, this is
for online hardware,
but do not give this thing now,
you should leave all these things for the workshop, I did
not know that those people had told me to
damage it here today and give the photo, I gave it,
but yes, my survey was done online from there itself,
first of all, I had made a
mistake, I did all that with the
motor and after fixing it, whatever was
changed, friend, the rear bumper is actually,
I will show you once, there is a
little more gum outside,
and the front
part [music] has been changed and this
extra fitting thing,
I removed it from the old one and installed it in the new one, for that they
took ₹1000,
think about it and
this process, they made
me go to hell in 11 days,
although in 10 days  The car was ready but
I could not go that day, so for this, but yes,
this process is
fine and I had to pay from my pocket, though you can see
around 1500, I had to pay 1400 for insurance
and I had to pay ₹1000 for the
extra fittings, the
cost of removing the old one and installing it in the new one,
so this process is
fine and the digital insurance is also
fine, there was
a man on WhatsApp, he said that
you have online insurance, I do
n't need to worry so much, if you have
Hero Deep insurance and your
workshop and if it is fine then there will
not be much problem, so this is the thing, so if
you have any question in this category, then
you can ask me in the
comments, so this is it, think about it, thank
you, expert signing of